Doni Darmawan

Jl. Garu II B, Harjosari I,Gg. Surya No.71 SS, Kec. Medan Amplas, Kota Medan, Sumatera Utara 20226 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/doni-darmawan/ | 0865761298781 | darmawandoni6@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Hi,

My name is Doni darmawan, I'm a Full Stack Developer that specialized in the Node JS Environtment, especially MERN Stack, I really like learn new things and really love to code:)

I'm currently focus on developing Front end using React JS.

Have experience from intensive 8 weeks Dumbways.id Bootcamp

Fell free to ask and contact me.

Best Regards.

EXPERIENCES

Amartha Microfinance

Software Engineer

(August 2021 - Present)

Jobs Desc:

- Riset and development new Feature
- Development at https://dashboard.amartha.com/
- Developer wordpress

TwisCode

Frontend Developer

(May 2020 - August 2021)

Jobs Desc:

- Building admin panel or landing page in React Js/ Next js
- Building website company in wordpress

EDUCATION

Altera Academy

Golang Developer

(July 2021 - August 2021)

- Fundamental Golang
- Rest API Golang
- Database Mysql

DumbWays.id

Full Stack JavaScript

(February 2020 - May 2020)

- Fundamental JavaScript
- Learn Front End with React Js
- Learn Back end With Express Js & Squelize

Mikrosil University

(August 2016 - December 2019)

Associate Management Informatika

3.78

SKILLS

React Js (9/10), Next Js (9/10), Express Js (7/10), SQL (9/10).

CERTIFICATIONS

CERTIFICATE GRADUATION

Alterra Academy

August 2020

For successfully completing Golang course

And graduated with " " Grade[]

With Final Project,

Satisfactory

Administrasi Hotel

CERTIFICATE GRADUATION

DumbWays.id

March 2020

who has succeeded and passed the Bootcamp Batch #14 in the Fullstack Javascript class.